<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="109" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://validation.gdn.giants-software.com/xml/fs25/modDesc.xsd">
    <author>CrankyAnt</author>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>AI Helper Refill Source Fix</en>
        <de>KI-Helfer Nachfüllquellen-Fix</de>
        <fr>Correctif des sources de remplissage de l'ouvrier IA</fr>
        <nl>AI-helper bijvulbron fix</nl>
    </title>

    <description>
        <en>
<![CDATA[
AI Helper Refill Source Fix

Fixes AI helper refill source selection for slurry, digestate, and manure spreaders.
It fixes three base game issues in the AI helper refill system:
- the settings menu can show one refill source while the helper uses another
- empty tanks or trailers can be treated as an unknown fill type and stop too early
- manure sources the active farm cannot access can appear selectable in multiplayer

Use this mod when you want AI helpers to refill from farm storages, animal pens, manure heaps, BGAs, or shared sources as intended.
The mod keeps the selected source synchronized between the menu, the game state, and multiplayer clients.
The mod hides inaccessible manure sources, so helpers do not stop with "Tank is empty!" after selecting a source that looks available but cannot be used.

For slurry spreaders that already contain digestate, the helper keeps using digestate when digestate is available in the selected slurry source.

This mod does not add new refill sources or storage capacity.
A storage or placeable still needs to be registered by the game as a valid helper refill source.

Multiplayer supported.
PC only, because it is a script mod.

Report issues on GitHub: https://github.com/CrankyAnt/FS25_AIHelperRefillSourceFix/issues

Changelog
Version 1.0.0.0
- Initial release
]]></en>
        <de>
<![CDATA[
KI-Helfer Nachfüllquellen-Fix

Behebt die Auswahl von Nachfüllquellen für KI-Helfer bei Gülle-, Gärreste- und Miststreuern.
Der Mod behebt drei Fehler im Nachfüllsystem der KI-Helfer:
- das Einstellungsmenü kann eine Nachfüllquelle anzeigen, während der Helfer eine andere verwendet
- leere Tanks oder Anhänger können als unbekannter Fülltyp behandelt werden und zu früh stoppen
- Mistquellen, auf die der aktive Hof keinen Zugriff hat, können im Mehrspielermodus auswählbar erscheinen

Nutze diesen Mod, wenn KI-Helfer wie vorgesehen aus Hoflagern, Tierhaltungen, Misthaufen, BGAs oder gemeinsam genutzten Quellen nachfüllen sollen.
Der Mod hält die ausgewählte Quelle zwischen Menü, Spielstatus und Mehrspieler-Clients synchron.
Der Mod blendet nicht zugängliche Mistquellen aus, damit Helfer nicht mit „Tank ist leer!“ stoppen, nachdem eine Quelle ausgewählt wurde, die verfügbar aussieht, aber nicht genutzt werden darf.

Bei Güllestreuern, die bereits Gärreste enthalten, verwendet der Helfer weiterhin Gärreste, wenn in der ausgewählten Güllequelle Gärreste verfügbar sind.

Dieser Mod fügt keine neuen Nachfüllquellen und keine zusätzliche Lagerkapazität hinzu.
Ein Lager oder platzierbares Objekt muss weiterhin vom Spiel als gültige Helfer-Nachfüllquelle registriert sein.

Mehrspielermodus wird unterstützt.
Nur für PC, da es sich um einen Script-Mod handelt.

Fehlerberichte auf GitHub: https://github.com/CrankyAnt/FS25_AIHelperRefillSourceFix/issues

Changelog
Version 1.0.0.0
- Erste Veröffentlichung
]]></de>
        <fr>
<![CDATA[
Correctif des sources de remplissage de l'ouvrier IA

Corrige la sélection des sources de remplissage des ouvriers IA pour les épandeurs de lisier, de digestat et de fumier.
Ce mod corrige trois problèmes du système de remplissage des ouvriers IA :
- le menu des paramètres peut afficher une source de remplissage pendant que l'ouvrier en utilise une autre
- les cuves ou remorques vides peuvent être traitées comme un type de remplissage inconnu et s'arrêter trop tôt
- les sources de fumier auxquelles la ferme active n'a pas accès peuvent apparaître comme sélectionnables en multijoueur

Utilisez ce mod si vous voulez que les ouvriers IA se remplissent comme prévu depuis des stockages de ferme, des bâtiments d'animaux, des tas de fumier, des BGA ou des sources partagées.
Le mod synchronise la source sélectionnée entre le menu, l'état du jeu et les clients multijoueur.
Le mod masque les sources de fumier inaccessibles, afin que les ouvriers ne s'arrêtent pas avec « Le réservoir est vide ! » après la sélection d'une source qui semble disponible mais ne peut pas être utilisée.

Pour les tonnes à lisier qui contiennent déjà du digestat, l'ouvrier continue à utiliser le digestat lorsque du digestat est disponible dans la source de lisier sélectionnée.

Ce mod n'ajoute pas de nouvelles sources de remplissage ni de capacité de stockage.
Un stockage ou objet plaçable doit toujours être enregistré par le jeu comme source de remplissage valide pour les ouvriers.

Multijoueur pris en charge.
PC uniquement, car il s'agit d'un mod script.

Signalez les problèmes sur GitHub : https://github.com/CrankyAnt/FS25_AIHelperRefillSourceFix/issues

Changelog
Version 1.0.0.0
- Première version
]]></fr>
        <nl>
<![CDATA[
AI-helper bijvulbron fix

Verhelpt de selectie van bijvulbronnen voor AI-helpers bij drijfmest-, digestaat- en mestverspreiders.
Deze mod verhelpt drie basegameproblemen in het bijvulsysteem van AI-helpers:
- het instellingenmenu kan een andere bijvulbron tonen dan de bron die de helper gebruikt
- lege tanks of aanhangers kunnen als onbekend filltype worden behandeld en te vroeg stoppen
- mestbronnen waar de actieve boerderij geen toegang toe heeft kunnen in multiplayer toch selecteerbaar lijken

Gebruik deze mod als je wilt dat AI-helpers zoals bedoeld bijvullen uit boerderijopslag, veestallen, mesthopen, BGA's of gedeelde bronnen.
De mod houdt de geselecteerde bron gelijk tussen het menu, de gamestatus en multiplayer-clients.
De mod verbergt ontoegankelijke mestbronnen, zodat helpers niet stoppen met "Tank is leeg!" nadat een bron is geselecteerd die beschikbaar lijkt, maar niet gebruikt mag worden.

Voor drijfmestverspreiders die al digestaat bevatten, blijft de helper digestaat gebruiken wanneer er digestaat beschikbaar is in de geselecteerde drijfmestbron.

Deze mod voegt geen nieuwe bijvulbronnen of opslagcapaciteit toe.
Een opslag of placeable moet nog steeds door de game zijn geregistreerd als geldige bijvulbron voor helpers.

Multiplayer wordt ondersteund.
Alleen voor PC, omdat dit een scriptmod is.

Meld problemen op GitHub: https://github.com/CrankyAnt/FS25_AIHelperRefillSourceFix/issues

Changelog
Versie 1.0.0.0
- Eerste release
]]></nl>
    </description>

    <iconFilename>icons/icon.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true" />

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/AIHelperRefillSourceFix.lua" />
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/AIHelperRefillSourceDebug.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>
</modDesc>
