<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="107" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://validation.gdn.giants-software.com/xml/fs25/modDesc.xsd">
    <author>CrankyAnt</author>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>AI Helper Refill Source Fix</en>
        <de>KI-Helfer Nachfüllquellen-Fix</de>
        <fr>Correctif des sources de remplissage de l'ouvrier IA</fr>
        <nl>AI-helper bijvulbron fix</nl>
    </title>

    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[AI Helper Refill Source Fix

This mod fixes base game issues with AI helper refill sources for slurry, digestate, and manure spreaders.

The mod keeps the refill source shown in the settings menu synchronized with the source actually used by the helper. This prevents helpers from drawing from a different storage than the one selected, or stopping with "Tank is empty!" while the selected source still contains material.

It also hides manure sources that the active farm cannot access, keeps multiplayer clients synchronized with the server after loading or joining, and keeps digestate active when a spreader is already using digestate and the selected source can supply it.

The mod does not add new refill sources. A storage or placeable still needs to be registered by the game as a valid helper refill source.

Multiplayer supported.
PC only, because it is a script mod.

Report issues on GitHub: https://github.com/CrankyAnt/FS25_AIHelperRefillSourceFix/issues

Changelog
Version 1.0.0.0
- Initial release]]></en>
        <de><![CDATA[KI-Helfer Nachfüllquellen-Fix

Dieser Mod behebt Basisspiel-Probleme mit Nachfüllquellen von KI-Helfern für Gülle-, Gärreste- und Miststreuer.

Der Mod hält die im Einstellungsmenü angezeigte Nachfüllquelle mit der Quelle synchron, die der Helfer tatsächlich verwendet. Dadurch wird verhindert, dass Helfer aus einem anderen Lager entnehmen als ausgewählt, oder mit „Tank ist leer!“ stoppen, obwohl die ausgewählte Quelle noch Material enthält.

Außerdem blendet der Mod Mistquellen aus, auf die der aktive Hof keinen Zugriff hat, hält Mehrspieler-Clients nach dem Laden oder Beitreten mit dem Server synchron und behält Gärreste bei, wenn ein Streuer bereits Gärreste verwendet und die ausgewählte Quelle sie liefern kann.

Der Mod fügt keine neuen Nachfüllquellen hinzu. Ein Lager oder platzierbares Objekt muss weiterhin vom Spiel als gültige Helfer-Nachfüllquelle registriert sein.

Mehrspielermodus wird unterstützt.
Nur für PC, da es sich um einen Script-Mod handelt.

Fehlerberichte auf GitHub: https://github.com/CrankyAnt/FS25_AIHelperRefillSourceFix/issues

Changelog
Version 1.0.0.0
- Erste Veröffentlichung]]></de>
        <fr><![CDATA[Correctif des sources de remplissage de l'ouvrier IA

Ce mod corrige des problèmes du jeu de base liés aux sources de remplissage des ouvriers IA pour les épandeurs de lisier, de digestat et de fumier.

Le mod synchronise la source affichée dans le menu des paramètres avec la source réellement utilisée par l'ouvrier. Cela évite que l'ouvrier puise dans un stockage différent de celui sélectionné, ou qu'il s'arrête avec « Le réservoir est vide ! » alors que la source sélectionnée contient encore du produit.

Il masque aussi les sources de fumier auxquelles la ferme active ne peut pas accéder, garde les clients multijoueur synchronisés avec le serveur après le chargement ou la connexion, et conserve le digestat lorsqu'un épandeur l'utilise déjà et que la source sélectionnée peut en fournir.

Le mod n'ajoute pas de nouvelles sources de remplissage. Un stockage ou objet placable doit toujours être enregistré par le jeu comme source de remplissage valide pour les ouvriers.

Multijoueur pris en charge.
PC uniquement, car il s'agit d'un mod script.

Signalez les problèmes sur GitHub : https://github.com/CrankyAnt/FS25_AIHelperRefillSourceFix/issues

Changelog
Version 1.0.0.0
- Première version]]></fr>
        <nl><![CDATA[AI-helper bijvulbron fix

Deze mod verhelpt basegame-problemen met bijvulbronnen voor AI-helpers bij drijfmest-, digestaat- en mestverspreiders.

De mod houdt de bijvulbron die in het instellingenmenu wordt getoond gelijk aan de bron die de helper werkelijk gebruikt. Daardoor wordt voorkomen dat helpers uit een andere opslag putten dan de geselecteerde bron, of stoppen met "Tank is leeg!" terwijl de geselecteerde bron nog materiaal bevat.

Daarnaast verbergt de mod mestbronnen waar de actieve boerderij geen toegang toe heeft, houdt hij multiplayer-clients na laden of joinen gelijk aan de server, en blijft digestaat actief wanneer een verspreider al digestaat gebruikt en de geselecteerde bron dat kan leveren.

De mod voegt geen nieuwe bijvulbronnen toe. Een opslag of placeable moet nog steeds door de game zijn geregistreerd als geldige bijvulbron voor helpers.

Multiplayer wordt ondersteund.
Alleen voor PC, omdat dit een scriptmod is.

Meld problemen op GitHub: https://github.com/CrankyAnt/FS25_AIHelperRefillSourceFix/issues

Changelog
Versie 1.0.0.0
- Eerste release]]></nl>
    </description>

    <iconFilename>icons/icon.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true" />

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/AIHelperRefillSourceFix.lua" />
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/AIHelperRefillSourceDebug.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>
</modDesc>
